Property Name	Geo Name	Source Country	Page Views
W Abu Dhabi Yas Island	*	India	"4,376"
"Emirates Palace Mandarin Oriental, Abu Dhabi"	*	India	"2,010"
Hilton Abu Dhabi Yas Island	*	India	"2,748"
Rixos Marina Abu Dhabi	*	India	772
Al Raha Beach Resort & Spa	*	India	"1,374"
Conrad Abu Dhabi Etihad Towers	*	India	"1,282"
"Radisson Blu Hotel, Abu Dhabi Yas Island"	*	India	"2,732"
"Crowne Plaza Abu Dhabi - Yas Island, an IHG hotel"	*	India	"2,238"
Qasr Al Sarab Desert Resort By Anantara	Emirate of Abu Dhabi	India	761
"InterContinental Abu Dhabi, an IHG Hotel"	*	India	704
Sheraton Abu Dhabi Hotel & Resort	*	India	728
"Traders Hotel, Qaryat Al Beri, Abu Dhabi"	*	India	620
"The Ritz-carlton, Abu-dhabi"	*	India	"1,290"
Le Méridien Abu Dhabi	*	India	724
Bab Al Qasr Hotel	*	India	458
"Radisson Blu Hotel & Resort, Abu Dhabi Corniche"	*	India	946
Premier Inn Abu Dhabi International Airport	*	India	898
"Royal Rose Abu Dhabi, a Curio Collection by Hilton Affiliated Hotel"	*	India	644
Centro Yas Island	*	India	"1,694"
Yas Island Rotana	*	India	"1,410"
Ramada by Wyndham Abu Dhabi Corniche	*	India	886
"The Wb Abu Dhabi, Curio Collection By Hilton"	*	India	"1,036"
Copthorne Downtown	*	India	690
Jannah Burj Al Sarab	*	India	886
Sofitel Abu Dhabi Corniche	*	India	674
City Seasons Al Hamra Hotel	*	India	830
"Shangri-la Qaryat Al Beri, Abu Dhabi"	*	India	744
Fairmont Bab Al Bahr	*	India	812
Erth Abu Dhabi	*	India	972
Millennium Downtown Abu Dhabi	*	India	592
Aloft Abu Dhabi	*	India	640
"Park Inn by Radisson Abu Dhabi, Yas Island"	*	India	"1,726"
The St. Regis Abu Dhabi	*	India	414
Corniche Hotel Abu Dhabi	*	India	770
Grand Hyatt Abu Dhabi Hotel & Residences Emirates Pearl	*	India	564
Tryp by Wyndham Abu Dhabi City Centre	*	India	626
Emirates Park Zoo & Resort	*	India	700
"Al Wathba, A Luxury Collection Desert Resort & Spa, Abu Dhabi"	*	India	562
"Marriott Hotel Downtown, Abu Dhabi"	*	India	690
Hawthorn Suites By Wyndham Abu Dhabi City Centre	*	India	464
Anantara Santorini Abu Dhabi Retreat	*	India	606
Novel Hotel City Center	*	India	464
"Marriott Hotel Al Forsan, Abu Dhabi"	*	India	972
Grand Millennium Al Wahda	*	India	494
Le Royal Méridien Abu Dhabi	*	India	636
Dusit Thani Abu Dhabi	*	India	532
"Holiday Inn Abu Dhabi, an IHG Hotel"	Abu Dhabi	India	223
Al Ain Palace Hotel	*	India	446
Novotel Abu Dhabi Al Bustan	*	India	690
"Staybridge Suites Abu Dhabi - Yas Island, an IHG hotel"	*	India	544